<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>


<!-- EN -->
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Music Meets Life</string>
    <string name="title">Music Meets Life</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>

    <string name="open_drawer">open_drawer world!</string>
    <string name="close_drawer">close_drawer</string>
    
    <string name="login">아이디</string>
    <string name="pass">비밀번호</string>
    <string name="login_success">Login Success</string>
    <string name="logout_success">You have been signed out</string>
    <string name="logout_asking">Are you sure you want to log out?</string>
    <string name="main_top_login">Please log in</string>
    <string name="main_sub_login">Login / Join</string>
    <string name="main_sub_logout">Logout</string>
    <string name="exit">Press the Back button to exit once more</string>
    <string name="error">error</string>
    <string name="language">Korean version</string>
    <string name="admin">Administrator Mode</string>
    <string name="general">Upload List</string>
    <string name="maintext1">Music,</string>
    <string name="maintext2">Meets Life.</string>
    <string name="send_message">Are you sure you want to transfer to the station?</string>
    <string name="send_success">The transfer is completed.</string>
    <string name="Wifi_Error">Please check your Wifi connection strength.</string>
    <string name="Canceling">Canceling...</string>
    <string name="send_cancel">Submit Cancel complete</string>
    
    
    <!-- Voice Recording -->
    <string name="voice_start">Start Voice Recording</string>
    <string name="voice_save"> save Success</string>
    <string name="voice_max">Voice Recording is up to 3 minutes</string>
    <string name="voice_send">It is being transferred ... This may take some time. It takes about 2-5 minutes.</string>
    
    <!-- Login -->
    <string name="service1">Terms of Service</string>
    <string name="service2">Personal Information Collection and Use Information</string>
    <string name="service1check">Please agree to the Terms of Service.</string>
    <string name="service2check">Please agree to the collection and use of personal information guide.</string>
    <string name="agree">Yes, I agree</string>
    
     <string name="pass_hint">8 or more characters</string>
    <string name="confirm_hint">Confirm password</string>
    <string name="join_success">Complete Sign Up</string>
    <string name="join_detail">Member information input</string>
    
    
    <!-- Video Recording -->
    <string name="video_start">Video shooting is possible for up to two minutes.</string>
    <string name="video_end">To end the recording.</string>
    <string name="video">Video recording is the default landscape mode shooting.\nShooting is possible for up to two minutes.</string>
    
    <!-- MyStudio -->
    <string name="mystudio_login">Please login first.\n Would you like to go to the login window?</string>
    <string name="delete_asking">Are you sure you want to delete?</string>
    <string name="choice">There are no videos selected.</string>
    <string name="share">Share</string>
    <string name="select">select</string>
    <string name="subject">subject</string>
    <string name="contents">Contents</string>
    
    
    <!-- dialog popup -->
    <string name="dialog_message">Wi-Fi 망이 아닐시에 데이터요금이 부가될수 있습니다.</string>
    <string name="ok">ok</string>
    <string name="cancel">cancel</string>
    <string name="downloadsize">\n 다운로드 사이즈 : </string>
    <string name="serial_success">시리얼 넘버가 확인되었습니다.</string>
    
    <!-- RecoderActivity -->
    <string name="noselectmusic">음악을 선택해 주세요.</string>
    <string name="start_rec">촬영을 시작합니다.</string>
    <string name="stop_rec">촬영을 종료합니다.</string>
    <string name="share">공유하기</string>
    <string name="no_path">뮤직비디오를 촬영해 주세요.</string>
    
    <!-- Youtube Post -->
    <string name="connection_error">서버와의 연결이 끊어졌습니다. 잠시후에 다시 연결하세요.</string>
    
    <string name="drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    
    
    <string name="notice1">
"1. Collect the company and contact \n
- Company Name: siepeu Korea \n
- Contact: 031) 819-9449 \n
- Hours: Monday to Friday (09:00 to 18:00), Sat / Sun / public holidays \n
- lunch hour (12:00 to 13:00) Telephone counseling is not \n
2. The personal data entry and collection methods to gather \n
Ltd. is a seamless customer service, we collect the following personal information for various services, such as data statistics. \n
A. General collector's item \n
1- phone number, and application services record, access logs and certification date, billing records, application version, carrier information, device information (model name, available memory, and file size, OS version, unique device identification number, etc.) \n
B. Personal Information Collection Methods \n
The company collects the first execution or application use when connecting to its network during and after application download personal information, some personal information is only collected when you subscribe to a particular application or a particular service. \n
\n
3. The purpose of collecting and using personal information \n
The company uses to collect and use personal information in the notice mentioned range for the following purposes, in principle, the same ranges used in excess without the prior consent of the users or not disclose your personal information to the outside world. (However, if a user is in accordance with the provisions of the Act and if the agreement with respect to personal information disclosed in advance or at the request of law enforcement agencies in accordance with established procedures on how the legislation has to be disclosed to the external investigation purposes.) \n
A. According to the identity verification service, personal identification, illegal use prevention and unauthorized use prevention of defective customer, certified doctor checking, record retention for dispute settlement, such grievance complaints handling, delivery notices \n
B. Develop new services, statistical characteristics, and ad serving services in accordance with, validation services, event and advertising information and participation opportunities, access frequency identification, statistics on customer service use \n
\n
5. The period of retention of personal information and use \n
A. In principle, personal information collected and used after the goal has been achieved without delay to destroy the information. However, if you need to be preserved in accordance with the provisions of relevant laws and regulations Company will keep your personal information for a certain period specified below. \n
\n
B. If you need to preserve in accordance with the provisions of relevant laws and regulations, including laws on consumer protection of e-commerce company keep customer information for a period of time determined by the relevant laws and regulations. In this case the company uses to keep the information only for the purpose of its storage and retention periods are listed below. \n
\n
Records relating to the display / Advertising \n
Conservation reasons: the law on Consumer Protection in Electronic Commerce \n
Retention Period: 6 months \n
Records regarding a contract or cancellation \n
Conservation reasons: the law on Consumer Protection in Electronic Commerce \n
Shelf life: 5 years \n
Records of payments and the supply of goods \n
Conservation reasons: the law on Consumer Protection in Electronic Commerce \n
Shelf life: 5 years \n
Records of consumer complaints or disputes processed \n
Conservation reasons: the law on Consumer Protection in Electronic Commerce \n
Retention period: 3 years \n
Record of landing \n
Conservation reasons: Communication Secrets Act \n
Retention Period: 3 months \n
\n
6. \n limitations of the services
The Company may collect personal information for a seamless Article 2 of the application service provider. If the user refuses to the company's personal information collection company can be a limitation on the use of all or part of the application service provided. \n    "</string>
    
    <string name="notice2">
"CHAPTER 1. GENERAL PROVISIONS \n
Article 1 (Purpose) \n
The agreement is that the siepeu Korea Co., Ltd. (the 'Company') in connection with the 'services' provided by using a wired and wireless network 'company' and 'membership' among forth the rights, duties, and other necessary matters The purposes. \n
\n
Article 2 (Definitions) \n
\n
Definition of terms used in this Agreement are as follows. \n
   1. The term 'services' refers to 'the Company' of websites, mobile sites, mobile applications, and other platforms, including through the provision to 'members' are applications, social networks, customer support, information and other services incidental thereto any it means. \n
   2. 'Member' means 'the Company' of the 'Service' signed a 'company' with the contract and in accordance with these terms and conditions by accessing the 'company' it means customers using augmented reality provides sound services. \n
   3. The term 'account' means 'members' in order to identify the 'service' use of 'Member' is decided, 'company' means a combination of letters and numbers that are approved. \n
   4. 'password' shall ensure that 'member' is consistent with the account has been granted 'Member' and 'Member' means a combination of letters or numbers specified for their personal privacy. \n
   5. 'paid services' means the various types of digital content (cache, items, including other paid content) and various services 'company' is available for a fee. \n
   6. 'post' means 'members' got in using a 'service' was posted on the 'service' code, letters, voice, sound and image and video information including in the form of articles, photos, videos and other files refers to the links. \n
\n
Article 3 (Terms and Conditions apply and change of) \n
\n
1- 'Company' is known to a 'member' in a manner that posted on the website (www.cftown.co.kr) of the contents of this Agreement, 'Member' is so easy to see the 'Service' initial screen or the 'Company'. \n
2- 'Company', 'e-commerce on consumer protection of the law', 'Law on the Regulation of the agreement ',' Promotion of Information and Communications Network Utilization and Information Protection Act', 'Content Industry Promotion Law' and other related laws and regulations and, if necessary, Guidelines of government agencies, within the scope of this agreement does not violate the recommendations may be revised. \n
3- 'Company' If you change the terms, by specifying the effective date and content of the notice in accordance with the revised terms to Article 11 paragraph 2 in the previous 7 days from the day their application. However, the 'members' if the terms of the amendment, you will notice a disadvantage in the same way in the 30 days prior to the date of application. \n
4- not agree to these terms, please visit our website on a regular basis 'Company' it means you agree to make changes to the Terms and Conditions. For damages of 'membership' occurs not knowing information about the changed terms 'company' can not be held responsible. \n
5- 'Member' If you do not consent to the application of the revised agreement, may refuse to apply the changed Terms and Conditions. The objection that 'member' for a change in the terms of 'service' can stop using and to terminate the contract (withdrawal). \n
6- When using the revised terms continue to apply after one 'service', 'Company', you agree to the revised terms. \n
Article 4 (accept other standards) \n
\n
1- 'Company' may determine the specific details not defined in this Agreement, including through operational policies, operational policies, such as in this case will have a complementary effect on this Agreement. \n
2- about the ahnihan details not specified in this Agreement and interpretation will follow the relevant laws and regulations or commercial practices. \n
\n
Conclusion of the contract Chapter 2 \n
\n
Article 5 (compliance with the limits of the contract) \n
1- services agreement and if you agree to the content of the 'members' have agreed on the contents of the self-read these Terms and Conditions which are then become the 'Company' and, depending on the application forms and procedures for designation, or to be presented at the beginning Terms of Service 'Company' will constitute a consent by the use for such application. \n
2- Those who 'members' is to become and be sure to use us as your real information, if it violates the 'Company', you can put limits on the use of rejecting the application or service is used. \n
3- 'Company' award is if there are no problems or technical work, the application is received by Service Net Augmented Reality sound principle that the consent use application. However, the 'Company' reserves the right to withhold consent or not to consent with respect to the following application for each call. \n
1. If the applicant has never lost the 'Members' qualifications previously by the Terms and Conditions. However, if you got the 'Company' in the 'Members', you consent to rejoin the exception. \n
2. If using another person's personal information \n
3. If the base of the false information, or 'the company' does not describe the information required by \n
4. 'members' are due to reasons attributable to the party to become non-approved or the company in violation of the matters specified when you apply for a grant of 'Member' qualified \n
5. 'Company' or afford the equipment in the event of a technical failure on \n
5- 'company' may have two to three minutes using a differential to use time, etc., using the number, the service menu, divided into grades according to the 'Company' policy for 'Members'. \n
7- 'company' with respect to 'members', 'Promotion of Information and Communications Network Utilization and Information Protection Act' and the 'Youth Protection Act' and can be used in accordance with limitations or age ratings and rating limits for compliance. \n
Article 6 (login and password) \n
1- 'Member' will be the best possible care not to expose their own account and password. Is responsible for the damage caused and results account and password has been exposed by the negligence of 'membership' 'membership' is to him. \n
2- If the 'Members' if stolen your account and password, or use a third party to promptly notify the 'Company' When I learned that you are in the guidance of the 'company' must follow them. \n
3- 'members' are required to change your password regularly to protect your account information, such as. \n
\n
\n
Article 7 (Provision of Information and Change) \n
\n
1- 'Member' shall provide true information to the 'company' can not be protected for the disadvantage caused by the false information provided, such as. \n
2- 'members' can modify the personal information you provide yourself. However, in some cases, you can disable this fix. \n
3- 'members' should be corrected as information changed through the Website, such as when the information is provided in the 'Company' change, without delay, the 'Services' page within the administration or the 'Company'. \n
4- 'company' for disadvantaged fails to notify changes to the 'company' is not responsible. \n
\n
Article 8 (protection and management of personal information) \n
\n
1- 'company' is committed to protecting the privacy of the bar 'Members' including the account information in accordance with applicable laws. 'Member' privacy and related laws for the use and the 'Company' will be subject to the privacy policy of announcing separately. \n
2- 'Company', 'Service' or of simply offering third party links, etc. Website 'Service.' For the 'Company' in this Privacy Policy does not apply. \n
3- 'Company' is not responsible for any information, including account information of 'Member' exposed due to reasons attributable to the 'Members'. However, if no geureohaji due to reasons attributable to the 'company'. \n
\n
Chapter 3 obligations of the contracting parties \n
(Obligations of the 'Company') Article 9 \n
\n
1- 'Company' is prohibited in the laws and regulations and these Terms and Conditions or do not act contrary to public morals, and endeavor to provide a continuous and reliable 'service'. \n
2- If vivacity failure in equipment or data, such as to repair or restore them without a lag when there is no compelling reason for the disappearance committed. \n
3- 'Company' build a security system to protect personal information in the 'Members' and must disclose the privacy policy and comply. \n
\n
(Duty of 'Member') Article 10 \n
1- 'Member' should not engage in the following actions. \n
1. 'Member' act of false information when registering to join us, or to change \n
2. the 'Company' staff, claiming to be an employee or official acts \n
3. The other 'members' of information theft or acts that can be used as abnormally 'company' is determined or suspected \n
4. Act to interfere with another person's 'service' used \n
5. 'Company' normal 'service' activities that interfere with the purpose of providing \n
6. For the purpose of neutralizing technological protection measures interfere with the normal operation of the app or the 'Company' is not supplied or approved ahnihan using a computer program, equipment or system behavior \n
7. exploits a bug in the app, or augmented reality in an unusual way, images, sound, action to acquire the video content, such as \n
8. act of a commercial activity with a 'service' without the prior consent of 'Company' \n
9. 'Member' trading accounts or accounts with others in augmented reality, image, sound, video content, such as trafficking and acts of others \n
10. 'Company' or third parties, such as sending the content that infringes copyright and other intellectual property rights, post, email or otherwise act in a way to disseminate to others \n
11. act clone 'services' the information obtained through the 'service' used by other purposes without prior consent of 'Company' or use it like publishing and broadcasting or given to third parties \n
12. other 'members' to harass, threaten or continue to suffer for a particular user, which acts for the inconvenience \n
13. offensive or transfer the personal information that may violate someone else's honor and privacy of the personal information, then, post, email or otherwise act in a way to disseminate to others \n
14. The public order and information of obscene information in violation of public morals, sentence, shape, sound, video transport, post, email or otherwise act in a way to disseminate to others \n
15. crimes and acts that are judged to be related objectively \n
16. Other acts in violation of the relevant laws and regulations \n
2- 'members' are required to ensure compliance with this Agreement including, operational policy announcements. \n
3- 'member' is in utilizing a 'service', 'member' of a person owns a mobile phone, tablet PC, and other mobile devices issued to another person, and shall not rent, management must not be lost. The terminal is delivered to others they own, rent, will not be held responsible 'company' for any problems as lost. \n
4- 'members' is to set a password, billing functions provided by each of the open market should be managed so as not to be made an illegal settlement. About the problems caused by not setting the password function, such as billing 'Company' is not responsible. \n
\n
Article 11 (Notification to 'Member') \n
1- 'Company', 'Member' If you notice about the electronic Unless otherwise stipulated in these Terms mail, message or SMS, alerts (Push Notification), can be notified using other electronic means. \n
2- 'Company' may be replaced in the 'Members' For more than seven days notice for the entire 'Company' in the 'Web Site' or the services within the 'Notice' paragraph (1) by posting notice on the screen. \n
\n
Chapter 4 Service \n
Article 12 (configuration of the service) \n
1- 'company' provides 'services' following a 'Member'. \n
   1. 'company' of the website, providing information through the mobile page \n
   2. Mobile 'service' through mobile applications (including mobile instant messaging platform that works with the 'Service') \n
   3. social community via mobile social platform 'Company', 'Service' \n
   4. Other 'Company' decides to offer 'membership', 'Service' \n
\n
Article 13 (Conditions of use of the mark and service identity) \n
\n
1- 'Company' and then publish the matters on the home page of the 'company', so that members can see them easily. However, you can ensure that privacy policies and terms be found through the 'Members', the connection screen. \n
   1. Mutual and representatives of name \n
   2. The office mailing address and e-mail address \n
   3. phone number, FAX number, \n
   4. company registration number, number of Android Apps \n
   5. Privacy Policy and Terms and Conditions \n
2- 'Company' in connection with the offer Augmented Reality source 'services' to the contents of the various types of content, information, terms and conditions, the minimum system specifications (OS), such as the use of rating the 'Company' in the homepage, open-market sales of each screen or help screen is displayed on. \n
3- In principle, 'Member' is purchased 'paid services' is the 'service' is available only in. However, when determining the policy of the open market or otherwise at each 'service', it's him. \n
4- purchase 'paid services', etc. If you need counseling about 'us' Customer Center (1588-4263), Main 1: 1. Please proceed with consultations, including through the contact \n
5- Others cancellation, is made to turn off / termination, compensation, use restrictions, etc., etc. as prescribed in the contract and follow other provisions of these terms and conditions or operating policies. \n
Article 14 (Provision of services and changes, interruption) \n
\n
1- 'Company' is a special rule for one year 24 hours a day without providing round the matter. \n
2- 'Company' is required on the modification of the policies and operations of some or all of the 'services' that are provided free of charge 'Company', stop, change, and thus expect a 'member' unless otherwise specified in the laws and regulations regarding loss of income, modification of the company's profits did not provide a free service provided by other direct loss, interruption, for damage caused by such changes are not a separate compensation. \n
3- In the following subparagraphs, despite claim 1, wherein the 'Company' can stop 'service.' \n
   1. Perform maintenance of computers, telecommunications equipment, replacement, periodic inspection, or if necessary modifications to the content of the information or 'Service' \n
   2. Electronic infringement of hacking incidents, accidents communication, 'member' of an unusual application behavior using, if necessary, in order to respond to unexpected realize the instability of the 'Service' \n
   3. For prohibiting the 'services' provided by a certain time or in a manner applicable law \n
   4. natural disasters, emergencies, power outages, 'services' of equipment failure or if the 'Service' impossible normal 'services' provided to the congestion of using \n
   5. 'Company' split, merger, transfer of business, the abolition of sales, is due to the art 'services' such as deterioration of earnings, 'company' in the management onto a great need \n
4- 'company' is to permanently shut down the 'service' four euros on a technical or management, 'Service' facts on the exit to exit after 30 days prior notice on the home page. \n
5- 'service' has to be terminated if 'members' can not claim damages for such free 'service' and do not use periods remain 'paid services'. If you do not see the use of the term or permanent 'paid services' to see the service until the end of a period. \n
6- during a temporary interruption or termination of the 'service', 'Company' will notify you in advance via the website. However, if there are special circumstances, you can be notified after the fact. \n
7- 'Company' 1 day 4 hours without prior notice to reasons attributable (cumulative time) or more continuous service if the failure has occurred is stopped or fixed-term fee-based services (fixed ticket, the term quantitative ticket goods, etc.) to stop the service only account and downtime extend the use of time corresponding to three times for free, and 'membership' can not be charged extra for damages against the 'Company'. 'Company' has stopped, but ADVISED service and the reasons for such failure to check the server, and if you stop the service downtime is extended beyond 10 hours has been exceeded by that time the use of free time, and 'membership' is About the 'Company' can not be billed separately for damages. \n
Article 15 (paid service) \n
\n
1- some or all of the 'company' has provided services can be provided for a fee, depending on the policy of 'company'. \n
2- If you want to use a 'paid service', 'membership' must be faithfully paid according to how the price set by the 'company' for use 'service fee'. \n
\n
Article 16 (Administration of the post) \n
\n
1- 'company' means 'member' in this case being registered to post or 'services' that determined that the prohibited acts prescribed in Article 10 about the posts or post content within delete them without notice or refuse to move or Register You can. \n
2- 'Company' published such information due to the board that operates the infringement of legal interests 'members' can request the deletion or placement of the contents of that information to refute the 'Company'. If the 'Company' is required to take action quickly, to notify the applicant. \n
(Reversion of Copyright and Rights) Article 17 \n
\n
1- Copyright and other intellectual property rights in the 'service' is attributed to the 'company'. However, the 'Members' work, such as provided under the 'posts' or partnership agreements are excluded. \n
2- 'Company' of the offer 'service' design, 'company' made the text, script (Script), graphics, and 'members' inter transmission functions such as 'Company,' provided that all the trademarks related to 'Services', Services marks, copyright and other intellectual property rights logo by the Republic of Korea and foreign laws and regulations 'Company' or has a 'company' are to the license. \n

3- 'member' is not that it retains ownership or copyright to the 'Service' under this agreement, 'company' from the 'Services' bar, which allows the use of the subject, 'member' of obtaining information on the 'Services' or Only private road is available in the form provided. \n
4- 'company' in conjunction with 'services', 'Member' to 'Company' in accordance with the terms and conditions set by the account, only give a voucher that can be used, such as content, and 'membership' is transferred for a ticket, sell, offer collateral You can not do any other act of disposal. \n
5- 'members' are specifically permitted contents and obtained through the 'Services' excluding 'members' use of state information for commercial purposes, duplication, distribution, or 'the company' created a text, script (Script), graphics , 'member' replicates the mutual inter-transmission capability, you can not retail. \n
6- 'Member' to 'service' and posts published within the search results, informative emails, and service 'company' the other 'service' to operate, can be exposed to promotions, with some modifications in the extent necessary for those exposed , replication, publication may be edited. If the 'Company' and comply with the terms of the Copyright Act, 'Members' whenever the customer centers or 'service' for deleting the post through my management, but the search results, you can take measures such as private. \n
7- 'Member' (including transport, broadcasting), is the work including the post of 'Company' obtained by using the 'service' any process without prior written consent of 'Company', duplication, public transmission, publication, distribution, issuing other way used by or distributed to the public, dissemination should hayeoseoneun. \n
8- civic 'members' of the post caused by the infringement of third party rights, including intellectual property rights • the criminal liability will be borne entirely 'members' own. \n
9- 'company' should be allowed the use of a work under copyright law when using the post method as 'members' of the other claim 6. \n
It 10- claim 6, wherein the 'Company' is valid for operating a 'service' and will continue to apply even after the withdrawal of the user. \n
\n
Article 18 (published offer of information and advertising) \n
\n
1- 'Company' methods such as e-mail or text messages sent, alerts (Push Notification) only 'members' posted throughout this Notice or banner a variety of information deemed necessary or agreed to receive 'Member' We can provide. \n
2- 'Company' may expose the 'Company' or third-party products, services and advertisements for such services in the 'services', 'Member' will agree. \n
3- for the loss and damage caused by 'Member' is a participation or advertising deals in the second paragraph, 'the company' does not bear any responsibility. \n
\n
Article 19 (collection of information) \n
\n
1- 'Company', you can save and keep the communications made within the 'services' such as chats. This information can not be viewed only receive or retain 'company' except to provide legitimate third party. 'Company' is a violation of Terms and Conditions • Act investigation, dispute resolution between 'members', and utilize this information, and only if necessary in order to maintain civil order processing or other 'services', 'Member for utilizing information, when material advantage The 'notice to. \n
2- 'Company', 'service' operations, such as terminal information of the stabilization program in order to improve the quality of the 'services', 'Member', to collect information such as information of the OS, you can take advantage of. \n
\n
Chapter 5 cancellation, contract termination and release • Restrictions on \n
\n
Article 20 (Withdrawal of offer) \n
\n
1- 'paid services' are classified as limited as possible the cancellation, this information will notice in a way that is easily understood when you purchased 'membership' is 'paid services'. \n
2- In case of cancellation of a possible 'paid services', 'Member' can be a cancellation within 7 days from the date of purchase. \n
3- In the following subparagraphs, the cancellation is restricted. \n
   1. If the items a la carte type \n
   2. Immediately after purchase, or if the items are used to start immediately applied to applications \n
   3. If the item acquired in the course of the free use of the 'Service' \n
   4. If the item being added benefit that provides additional benefits has been used \n
   5. If the item sold is part of a bundle type used \n
   6. Use or to see the opening act in the case of a capsule-type items that are opened when the utility determines the \n
4- If the 'service fee' advertising content and the content is displayed in the • different or if the agreement with the request is made within 3 days from the date of purchase, or 'paid services' availability, from the day that the fact was not me or unknown 30 You can withdraw an offer within days. \n
5- If minors have purchased a 'paid service' without the consent of the legal guardian, or legal representative of a minor, you can cancel the payment. However, if the minor is believed to seongnyeonja using such principalities and can be canceled restrictions, 'Paid Services' whether the buyer is a minor, whether based on the method of payment terminals, etc. myeonguija of the advanced payment of 'paid services' The judgment. \n
6- 'Member' (including electronic documents), by telephone or in writing, you can withdraw an offer in the way of such e-mail. \n
7- hayeotgeona 'Company' is free of charge to paying 'members' and the other 'members', 'Paid Services' are excluded from receiving gifts of the cancellation. \n
\n
(Effect of cancellation) Article 21 \n
\n
1- 'Member' If you have to withdraw an offer, 'the company' is recovered or delete the 'paid services' of 'membership' without delay and cancellation on the open market payment provider within three business days from the date of receipt of the necessary documents, including a refund to initiate the necessary procedures to request such a refund. \n
2- 'Company' got the payment as reimbursement payments 'Member' is a credit card or else 'Act on Consumer Protection in Electronic Commerce' as the payment method to determine if a payment provided by the relevant payment methods without delay It allows the operator will ask you to stop or cancel the claim of Payment. However, when receiving the 'Company' are paid from the already cash settlement agent settlement agent must refund it to the consumer notifies them. \n
3- 'Company' can be charged to a case such as this, some used or consumed item, the 'members' have gained an amount equivalent to any interest or costs on the supply of the item 'Member'. \n
4- 'company' may require the documents needed for reimbursement to the 'Members' if necessary, 'members' may be refused if there is restricted reimbursement. \n
\n
Article 22 (Cancellation and Termination of the Agreement) \n
\n
1- 'member' may terminate the service contract as a matter of 'Member'. \n
2- 'Member' If you want to terminate your contract, you should apply for the withdrawal of 'company' in accordance with the prescribed procedure to establish 'membership'. \n
3- If 'members' are in violation of the duties of 'Member' set forth in these Terms and Conditions 'Company', you can terminate the contract after the notice of the 'Member' or restrict 'services' used for a certain period of time. However, the 'members' violated the law, if intentional or gross negligence inflicting damage on the 'Company', you can terminate the contract without notice. \n
4- 'Member' Specific details of the restrictions that may be in violation of this Section 3 can be found through the jimyeo determined in accordance with the policies of the operating policies, such as 'Company', 'Company' HOME. \n
5- If the contract is terminated in accordance with paragraph 3 clue, 'members' are 'paid services' can not lose the permission to refund and charge the resulting damages. \n
6- If the 'Company' is used to terminate the contract, 'the company' will inform the 'Members' by methods such as e-mail or text messages sent to the 'Members'. \n
\n
Article 23 (blackout) \n
\n
1- 'Company', 'Member', the following can limit the 'service' use restrictions and may take legal action and appointed to terminate the contract or term of service of 'membership' without prior notice if the reasons for each of the You can. \n
   1. If you steal someone else's phone numbers and personal information \n
   2. The staff of the 'company', if you impersonate an employee or representative \n
   3. If using for commercial purposes a 'company' of the 'Service' \n
   4. If the act of sharing with others, or marketing information cereal augmented reality content of 'Member' \n
   5. If you knowingly take the gain using the error (Bug) of the application \n
   6. 'Company' of technological protection measures to be armed or interfere with the normal operation of the application to 'company' have not provided or approved malicious / illegal program, illegal communications, access rights, etc. If you provide more than acts or use \n
   7. public order and information of obscene information in violation of public morals, sentence, shape, sound, video transmission, publication, dissemination to others if you are in the way of electronic mail or any other \n
   8. someone else's honor, Model, what can be a violation of the personal information transmission, publication, electronic mail or any other method of dissemination to other users when you \n
   9. The other 'members' to harass, threaten or continue to suffer for a particular user, if the conduct that the inconvenience \n
   10. other 'members' of the 'Services' interfere with the use of offensive or abusive, profane use, obscene words, if you like sex depicted \n
   11. insults that hinder the social order and public morals, obscene contents, if you use a name (character name, account name, Nickname, etc.) \n
   12. If the other normal 'service' activity is inhibited in the operating \n
   13. If a violation of other laws and regulations \n
2- 'Company' conditions and details of ahnihan use limits, use restrictions, and not specified in subparagraphs subparagraphs of the preceding paragraph is defined as the operating policies of each of the 'service'. \n
3- 'Company', 'Member' If you continue to not sign more than three months, 'members' can be used to limit the effectiveness of protection and management of information. \n
4- 'Company' will inform the 'Member' limit the use of the Services or if you terminate the contract, through the official channels of the e-mail application or the initial screen or application services to the 'Member' 'Members'. \n
5- 'members' can appeal within 15 days from the date of the blackout in accordance with the procedures established by the 'company' for such limited use. If the objection is justified when it is approved by the 'company' to resume the use of a 'company' immediately 'service'. \n
Article 24 (Appeals) \n
\n
'Company' means 'members' are quickly processed within a reasonable period of time when it is deemed justified complaints or objections raised. However, for a long period of time it is required to process a 'member' of reasons and schedules that take a long time to 'Company' notice on the home page or to notify by e-mail, telephone or in writing, such as. \n
\n
Article 6 damages and refunds, etc. \n
\n
Article 25 (Damages) \n
\n
1- 'company', 'company' in connection with the offer 'services' does not assume any responsibility for damages incurred by 'members'. However, in the case of damage caused intentionally or by gross negligence of the 'company' is excluded. \n
2- The 'members' are in violation of this Agreement has had a loss in the 'Company', 'Member' is 'company' with respect to the responsibility to compensate for that damage. \n
\n
Article 26 (refundable) \n
\n
1- If the cause of an offer to withdraw due to reasons attributable to the 'Members' Remorse of 'membership' has deducted 10% of the refund amount in settlement fees and other expenses with paragraph 3 of Article 19 as a refund fee income and The refunds. \n
2- except for a defect of the purchased item with respect to payments made to function through gift and refund shall in principle not available, a refund is due to defects of the item can be sent only to the present user. \n
3- refund may be restricted to terminate the contract if the reasons attributable to the current legislation and significant violation of terms such as 'members'. \n
\n
Article 27 (Fri mistakes) \n
\n
1- 'Company' will be refunded the full amount of gold in the same way as billing mistake of using the gold price in the event of a mistake. However, when the refund in the same manner impossible to notice it in advance. \n
2- 'Company' is a responsible reason for the mistake that occurred Friday 'Company', you are refunded the cost of the contract, regardless of the mistakes of gold full fee. However, 'Member' is a responsible reason for the mistake that occurred Friday, the 'Company' is required to refund the costs will be borne by mistake Gold 'membership' is within a reasonable range. \n
3- 'Company' is responsible to prove that the payment be imposed on the parties to use if you refuse a refund for the gold mistake to claim that 'members'. \n
\n
Article 28 (Dispute Resolution and Grievance) \n
\n
1- 'company' means 'members' to consider the convenience of the members of the opinions or how to present a complaint to guide the initial screen in the application or service website. 'The company' to operate a dedicated organization for handling complaints and opinions of these 'members'. \n
2- 'Company' is quickly processed within a reasonable period of time if it is deemed to be objectively justified opinions or complaints that arise from the 'Members'. However, if long-term treatment is required for a 'membership' to the reasons and schedules that take a long-term 'services' such notice through my announcements or notifications by e-mail, telephone or in writing, such as. \n
3- 'company' and if 'Member' to adjust the dispute is a dispute arises between regulatory authorities in the third company in good faith and prove limited measures, such as restrictions to the use of 'Member', may be subject to adjustments adjustments agency. \n
4- 'Company' Customer Service hours of operation are: to operate. \n
   1. Operating Hours: 09:00 ~ 18: 00 \n
   2. workdays: from Monday to Friday (Saturdays, Sundays and public holidays excluded) \n
\n
(Exemption of the 'Company'), Article 29 \n
\n
1- 'Company' exhibit, affairs, natural disasters, emergencies, is currently the responsibility of the technology will be waived if you can not provide services to a technical defect that can not be solved other force majeure reason. \n
2- 'Company' Stop, responsible for the use disorders and termination of the exemption 'members' due to reasons attributable to the 'service'. \n
3- 'Company' period to stop the carrier telecommunication services or does not provide the normal responsibilities without intention or gross negligence of a 'Member' for the case damage has occurred to the 'Company' are exempt. \n
4- 'Company' known in advance 'service' for the repair of equipment, replacement, periodic inspection, construction, etc., unless intention or gross negligence of the 'services' for the case where a failure has occurred is stopped or the 'Company' to unavoidable reasons This responsibility is waived. \n
5- 'company' is exempt from responsibility for problems due to various problems or the 'Company' in the network environment, intentionally or not gross negligence arising from a mobile network, or a mobile device environment of 'Member'. \n
6- 'Company', 'Member' or a third party 'services' within or the 'Company' published on the website or sent the information, data and reliability of the facts, the accuracy of intentional or gross negligence 'company' for the content of such no one is exempt from this responsibility. \n
7- 'company' means 'member' or between 'members' and the third no obligation to intervene in the dispute 'Services' via the tracking no responsibility to compensate for the resulting damage. \n
8- For the 'Company' offer 'services' of free service, unless intention or gross negligence of the 'company', 'company' is not an indemnity. \n
9- The 'service' may be provided through a part of the 'services' provided by 'services' that other operators, and the 'company' is provided by other operators 'service' for such damages resulting from 'the Company' or it is exempt from this responsibility without gross negligence. \n
10- 'company' means 'member' With this augmented reality services and sources do not get to be responsible for the consequences of such a character, experience, items, or expected loss, arising from use of the eclectic or 'Services' liability for damages and no intentional or gross negligence of the 'company' is exempt. \n
11- 'Company', 'member' of the application on cyber assets (content information), grade / loss responsibility with respect to pitting with no intention or gross negligence of a 'company' are exempt. \n
12- 'Company', 'member' of the mobile device in the event the damage caused by errors or inaccurate personal information and e-mail addresses listed, or not shown to have no damage is intentional or gross negligence 'Company' About the event This responsibility is waived. \n
13- 'Company' is relevant laws and regulations, according to government policy, according to the 'Service' or 'member', 'service' may restrict the use of time, etc., which occurs in accordance with these restrictions and limitations, 'service' used in matters related For this responsibility is waived. \n
\n
Article 30 (Governing Law and Jurisdiction) \n
\n
This agreement is governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of the Republic of Korea, the 'Company' case and the 'Member' in the dispute between that litigation, the competent court is the court in accordance with the procedure set out in the statute. \n
\n
Laws \n
1. This agreement is implemented from December 01 2014. \n
\n"
    </string>
    

    
    <!-- temp -->
    <string name="app_description">Vuforia Books Sample Applications</string>
    <string name="button_start">Start</string>
    <string name="button_OK">OK</string>
    <string name="string_$">$</string>
    <string name="string_openParentheses">(</string>
    <string name="string_closeParentheses">)</string>
    <string name="string_ratings">ratings</string>
    <string name="status_bar_scanning">Scanning</string>
    <string name="content_desc_vuforia_logo">Vuforia Logo</string>
    <string name="content_desc_vuforia_background">Vuforia Background</string>
    <string name="book_data_your_price">Your Price</string>
    <string name="content_description_cover">Cover</string>
    <string name="content_description_strike">Strike</string>
    <string name="content_description_background">Background</string>
    <string name="book_data_touch_for_more">Touch for more information</string>
    <string name="UPDATE_ERROR_AUTHORIZATION_FAILED_TITLE">Authorization Error</string>
    <string name="UPDATE_ERROR_PROJECT_SUSPENDED_TITLE">Authorization Error</string>
    <string name="UPDATE_ERROR_NO_NETWORK_CONNECTION_TITLE">Network Unavailable</string>
    <string name="UPDATE_ERROR_SERVICE_NOT_AVAILABLE_TITLE">Service Unavailable</string>
    <string name="UPDATE_ERROR_UPDATE_SDK_TITLE">Unsupported Version</string>
    <string name="UPDATE_ERROR_TIMESTAMP_OUT_OF_RANGE_TITLE">Clock Sync Error</string>
    <string name="UPDATE_ERROR_REQUEST_TIMEOUT_TITLE">Request Timeout</string>
    <string name="UPDATE_ERROR_BAD_FRAME_QUALITY_TITLE">Poor Camera Image</string>
    <string name="UPDATE_ERROR_UNKNOWN_TITLE">Service Unavailable</string>
    <string name="UPDATE_ERROR_AUTHORIZATION_FAILED_DESC">The cloud recognition service access keys are incorrect or have expired.</string>
    <string name="UPDATE_ERROR_PROJECT_SUSPENDED_DESC">The cloud recognition service has been suspended.</string>
    <string name="UPDATE_ERROR_NO_NETWORK_CONNECTION_DESC">Please check your internet connection and try again.</string>
    <string name="UPDATE_ERROR_SERVICE_NOT_AVAILABLE_DESC">The service is unavailable, please try again later.</string>
    <string name="UPDATE_ERROR_UPDATE_SDK_DESC">The application is using an unsupported version of Vuforia.</string>
    <string name="UPDATE_ERROR_TIMESTAMP_OUT_OF_RANGE_DESC">Please update the date and time and try again.</string>
    <string name="UPDATE_ERROR_REQUEST_TIMEOUT_DESC">The network request has timed out, please check your internet connection and try again.</string>
    <string name="UPDATE_ERROR_BAD_FRAME_QUALITY_DESC">The camera does not have enough detail, please try again later.</string>
    <string name="UPDATE_ERROR_UNKNOWN_DESC">The service is unavaiable, please try again later.</string>

    <string name="splash_screen_description">Vuforia Splash</string>
    
    
    <string name="INIT_ERROR">Error</string>
    <string name="INIT_ERROR_DEVICE_NOT_SUPPORTED">Failed to initialize Vuforia. This device is not supported.</string>
    <string name="INIT_ERROR_NO_CAMERA_ACCESS">Failed to initialize Vuforia. Camera not accessible</string>
    <string name="INIT_LICENSE_ERROR_MISMATCH_KEY">Vuforia App key is not valid for this product. Please get a valid key, by logging into your account at developer.vuforia.com and choosing the right product type during project creation.</string>
    <string name="INIT_LICENSE_ERROR_MISSING_KEY">Vuforia App key is missing. Please get a valid key, by logging into your account at developer.vuforia.com and creating a new project.</string>
    <string name="INIT_LICENSE_ERROR_INVALID_KEY">Invalid Key used. Please make sure you are using a valid Vuforia App Key.</string>
    <string name="INIT_LICENSE_ERROR_NO_NETWORK_TRANSIENT">Unable to contact server. Please try again later.</string>
    <string name="INIT_LICENSE_ERROR_NO_NETWORK_PERMANENT">No network available. Please make sure you are connected to the Internet.</string>
    <string name="INIT_LICENSE_ERROR_CANCELED_KEY">This app license key has been canceled and may no longer be used. Please get a new license key.</string>
    <string name="INIT_LICENSE_ERROR_UNKNOWN_ERROR">Failed to initialize Vuforia.</string>
    
    
    <string name="hint_title">Title</string>
    <string name="hint_singer">Singer</string>
    <string name="hint_company">Company</string>
    <string name="hint_price">Price</string>
    <string name="hint_home">Home</string>
    <string name="hint_youtube">youtube</string>
    <string name="hint_video">video</string>
    <string name="hint_photo">photo</string>
</resources>
